http://www.cetasoft.net/privacypolicy

Home
Features
Our Clients
Contact Us
Privacy PolicyCETA Software Limited and its subsidiaries (“we“, “us”, “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) and any other documents referred to herein, sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting the websites we operate, cetasoft.net, cetacloud.tv, ceta.tv, cetacloud.com. cetasoft.tv and icfm.tv, (together “Sites”) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.DATA CONTROLLERFor the purposes of the Data Protection Act 2018 and Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016, (“GDPR”) or any subsequent amendment or replacement or supplementary legislation (together “Data Protection Law”), the data controller is CETA Software Limited of 3 Meadow Court, Witney, Oxfordshire, OX28 6ER, England.LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSINGWe collect and use the personal data described below in order to provide you with access to our Sites and Services in a reliable and secure manner. We also collect and use personal data:For our legitimate business needs.To fulfil our contractual obligations to you.To comply with our legal obligations.To the extent we process your personal data for any other purposes, we ask for your consent in advance or require that our partners obtain such consent.INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOUWe may collect and process the following information about you:Information you give us. When using the Sites you may give us information about you by filling in forms on our Sites or by corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our Sites, apps, subscribe to our services (“Services”) or newsletter, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our Sites, and when you report a problem with our Sites or Services.The information you give us may include your first name and last name, address, email address, mobile phone number, phone number, and address.Information we collect about you. With regard to each visit to our Sites or use of our Services we may automatically collect the following information about you:Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;Tracking information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Sites (including date and time); page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.Information we receive from other sources. We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. In this case we will have informed you when we collected that data that it may be shared internally and combined with data collected on the Sites or via the Services.We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.COOKIESWe use cookies on our Sites and within the Services to distinguish you from other users of the Sites and Services. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Sites and use our Services  and also allows us to improve our Sites and Services.What are cookiesCookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the website. Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies.We use persistent cookies and session cookies on our Sites and Services.Persistent CookiesA persistent cookie is stored on a user’s device in between browser sessions which allows the preferences or actions of a user across our Sites (or in some cases across different websites) to be remembered. We use persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Sites or Services.Session CookiesA session cookie allows the Sites or Services to link your actions during a browser session. We use session cookies to enable certain features of the Sites or Services, to better understand how you interact with the Sites or Services and to monitor aggregate usage by users and web traffic routing on the Sites. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Sites or Services and then close your browser.Which cookies we use and whyThe table below explains the cookies we use and why we use each of them.CookieTypePurposeNewRelicAnalytics cookiesThese cookies allow an analysis of your usage. The information stored by the cookie about your use of this website (including your IP address, location and pages visited) will be transmitted to a server of NewRelic.  It allows us to track problems in our code and to measure the performance of our application. You can read the full New Relic privacy policy at:https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacyRegistrationSign-in cookiesWhen you sign in, we generate cookies that let us know whether you are signed in or not. Our servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with.Site PerformancePreference cookiesWe occasionally use site performance cookies to remember preferences you may have set on our Sites.You can set up your browser options, to stop your computer accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use the whole of our Sites or all functionality of the Services.To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Do not trackWe do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.USES MADE OF THE INFORMATIONWe use information held about you in the following ways.Information you give to us. We will use this information:To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;To provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired, about unless you have opted not to receive such information;We will only permit selected third parties to contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this by ticking the relevant consent box situated on the form on which we collected your data;To notify you about changes to our Services;To ensure that content from our Sites and Services is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.Information we collect about you. We will use this information:To administer our Sites and Services and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;To inform you about scheduled Services downtimes and new features;To improve our Sites and Services to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer;To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Sites and Services, when you choose to do so;As part of our efforts to keep our Sites and Services safe and secure;To monitor your use of the Sites and Services is in compliance with any legal agreements with have with you;To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Sites or Services about our goods or services that may interest you or them.Information we receive from other sources. We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).We will not sell or rent your personal data to anyone.DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATIONInformation we share with third parties. We may share your information with selected third parties including:Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Sites and Services.Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.Information we disclose to third parties. We may disclose your personal data to third parties:In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.If we or a member of our group of companies or substantially all of their assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by them about their customers will be one of the transferred assets.If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our and/or any other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, safety, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATAOur Services are global and your information (including personal data) may be stored and processed in any country where we have operations or where we engage service providers, and we may transfer your information to countries outside of your country of residence, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country of residence.The personal data that we collect from you may therefore be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA“). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers or partners. Such staff or subcontractors may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details or the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing outside of the EEA.We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In particular, this means that your personal data will only be transferred to a country that provides an adequate level of protection (for example, where the European Commission has determined that a country provides an adequate level of protection) or where the recipient is bound by standard contractual clauses according to conditions provided by the European Commission (“EU Model Clauses”).Our Sites and Services are accessible via the internet and may potentially be accessed by anyone around the world. Other users may access the Sites or Services from outside the EEA. This means that where you chose to post your data on our Sites or within the Services, it could be accessed from anywhere around the world and therefore a transfer of your data outside of the EEA may be deemed to have occurred. You consent to such transfer of your data for and by way of this purpose.PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATIONAll information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any credit card information or payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Sites or Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share any password with anyone.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will endeavour to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Sites or the Services. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESOur Sites and Services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.YOUR RIGHTSYou have the right under Data Protection Law, free of charge, to request:Access to your personal data.Rectification or deletion of your personal data.A restriction on the processing of your personal data.Object to the processing of your personal data.A transfer of your personal data (data portability) in a structured, machine readable and commonly used format.Withdraw your consent to us processing your personal data, at any time.You can make a request in relation to any of the above rights by contacting us as set out at the end of this Privacy Policy. We will respond to such queries within 30 days and deal with requests we receive from you, in accordance with the provisions of Data Protection Law.MARKETING COMMUNICATIONSPlease note that where we process your personal data for marketing purposes, if you change your mind about being contacted in the future, you can also “opt out” at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email. Once you “opt out”, you will no longer receive any marketing emails from us. We will continue to communicate with you regarding your service billing and support via email.We send push notifications from time to time in order to update you about any service updates, events and promotions we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please disable these in the settings on your device.DATA RETENTIONWe retain personal data for as long as necessary for the relevant activity for which it was provided or collected. This will be for as long as we provide access to the Sites or Services to you, your account with us remains open or any period set out in any relevant contract you have with us. However, we may keep some data after your account is closed or you cease using the Sites or Services for the purposes set out below.We usually delete personal data 90 days after your agreement with us has terminated. However, we may retain personal data where reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, resolve disputes, enforce our Terms and Conditions, or fulfil your request to “unsubscribe” from further messages from us.We will retain de-personalised information after your account has been closed.Please note: After you have closed your account or deleted information from your account, any information you have shared with others will remain visible. We do not control data that other users may have copied from the Sites or Services. Your profile may continue to be displayed in the services of others (e.g. search engine results) until they refresh their cache.COMPLAINTSIf you have any complaints about our use of your personal data please contact us as set out at the end of this Privacy Policy or contact our supervisory authority in the UK:The Information Commissioner’s Office at, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, England (“ICO”).AGE OF USERSThe Sites and the Services are not intended for and shall not be used by anyone under the age of 16.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYAny changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy was last updated on 25th February 2020 and replaces any other Privacy Policy previously applicable from this date.CONTACTQuestions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to:By post: CETA Software Limited, 3 Meadow Court, Witney, Oxfordshire, OX28 6ER, EnglandBy email: info@cetasoft.net
